http://www.sidharvey.com/wps/portal/c/terms

X
Current Selected Location - Sid Harvey Garden City (0999) Garden City NY
If you liked to order from a different location, please select from below
Switching Accounts
Are you sure you want to switch accounts?
Switching Accounts
Switching accounts in the middle of an order will clear your current cart. Are you sure you want to switch accounts?
Switching Locations
Are you sure you want to switch locations?
Switching Locations
Switching locations in the middle of an order will clear your current cart. Are you sure you want to switch locations?
Z7_JA82HK02LOSB40AT2ECEJR00K7
/wps/contenthandler/!ut/p/digest!-bHWyL0K4-dEGkmsY_Ou5A/pm/oid:--portletwindowid--@oid:Z6_JA82HK02LOSB40AT2ECEJR0046
/wps/contenthandler/!ut/p/digest!-bHWyL0K4-dEGkmsY_Ou5A/um/secure/currentuser/profile?expandRefs=true
Refrigerant Regulators
Valves & Refrigeration (Globe,Chk, Ball)
Line Set Covers
Misc A/C/R/Accessories
Ice Machine Parts (Oem Only)
Compressor Parts & Misc.
A/C Unit Parts (OEM Only)
Pressure Controls Steam
Flow Controls(Sail Switch & Pad)
Temperature Controls
Snap Disc Fan limit
Water Control Valves (Cooling)
Heating Parts
Heating Parts (Oil & Gas)
Refrigeration Oils
Refrigeration Oil (Synthetic)
General Cleaning Chemicals
Lubricants
Boiler Chemicals
Acid Test Kits
Mastic (Adhesives)
Remanufactured Pumps & Bearing Accessories
Remanufactured Boiler Controls (Feeders Etc.)
Remanufactured Boiler Ctrl Temp (Aquasta)
Other Power Tools
Hand Tools (General Use)
Hand Tools (Sheetmetal)
Batteries
Tube Cleaning Tool (Sand Cloth)
Torches - Torch Kits & Accs
Tanks (Welding Gas)
Refrigeration Parts
Refrigeration Unit Parts (Oem Only)
Accumulators, Rec, Mufflers Etc.
Fujitsu Accs
Condensing Units A/C (Comm.)
Gas Burners Commercial
Gas Valves (Commercial & Residential)
Terms of Use
TermsDeliveryService ChargeTaxesReturn Of GoodsLimited WarrantyRe-Manufactured ExchangeChanges to terms and ConditionsPrivacy PolicyFreight PolicyTERMS OF ACCESS
Terms
All sales are F.O.B. Sid Harvey branch location and are offered at wholesale to the trade only. All charge invoices are due and payable net on the 10th of the month following date of purchase, or as agreed to in writing.
Top
Delivery
Orders receive immediate attention. All shipments will be made via the route we consider best, unless your order specifies method of shipment.
Top
Service Charge
Service charges will be assessed at a rate of 1-1/2% per month or the highest rate allowed by law (whichever is the lesser), from the due date of each invoice to date of payment.
Top
Taxes
Orders are accepted with the understanding any applicable taxes will be added, as the law requires. If we fail to charge you tax where applicable, we reserve the right to invoice you for tax at a later date.
Top
Return Of Goods
No goods or materials will be accepted for return without our written consent. Special, non-cataloged material is not returnable. All accepted returns are subject to a 15% restocking charge.
Top
Limited Warranty
New Items: We extend the manufacturer’s warranty on every unit or equipment sold by us to persons or organizations who purchase such units or equipment from us for resale. This manufacturer’s warranty does not cover merchandise that has been damaged by improper application or installation, careless handling, water or fire damage, or other conditions beyond our control.THE FOREGOING CONSTITUTES THE ENTIRE WARRANTY WITH RESPECT TO SUCH UNITS OR EQUIPMENT AND IS IN LIEU OF ALL OTHERS EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY AND WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. IN NO EVENT IS SID HARVEY’S RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER.Sid Harvey Remanufactured Items: Every unit or equipment remanufactured by Sid Harvey’s is warrantied to be free from defects in material and workmanship for a period of two years after shipment from our factory. Units claimed to be defective within the warranty period must be returned to us, transportation prepaid. If found defective they will be repaired and replaced for no additional charge. No units or equipment will be replaced in advance of our inspection.THE FOREGOING CONSTITUTES THE ENTIRE WARRANTY WITH RESPECT TO REMANUFACTURED UNITS OR EQUIPMENT AND EXTENDS ONLY TO PERSONS OR ORGANIZATIONS WHO PURCHASE FROM US FOR RESALE AND IS IN LIEU OF ALL OTHER WARRANTIES EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY AND WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. IN NO EVENT IS SID HARVEY’S RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER.
Top
Re-Manufactured Exchange
Remanufactured units are sold, at the prices listed, only on exchange for an old unit of the same model.REMANUFACTURED ADVANCE REPLACEMENTFor your convenience, and subject to the limitations of our stock, we will ship a remanufactured replacement in advance of receiving the old unit if you so request. It is important of course, that identification be accurate. Many parts remanufactured by Sid Harvey’s are no longer available new, and therefore the units become "priceless" to us. As a result, we will bill you an advance replacement charge when the remanufactured item is shipped. Upon receipt by us of the old unit, we will refund or credit to your account the amount of the advance replacement charge.
Top
Changes to terms and Conditions
Terms and conditions subject to change without notice.
Top
Privacy Policy
Our customers are our most important asset and, as such, we would like to set forth the following policies that we strictly adhere to:RELEASE OF DATA We will never release, sell, or give a customer’s name or email address to any other party or organization without the customer’s explicit permission unless we are required to do so by law or we, in good faith, believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of Sid Harvey’s Web site; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our customers, our employees or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false registration information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you – including your computer's IP address -- may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions.)THIRD PARTY LINKS Web site visitors should be aware that this privacy policy only governs Sid Harvey’s Web site, and does not govern sites accessible via links from Sid Harvey’s Web site. When you are directed to another site via a link of any type, you should be aware that you will have left the Sid Harvey Web site. These other sites may send their own "cookies" to you and collect data or solicit personal information pursuant to policies that are not consistent with our Privacy Policy. For this reason, we strongly urge you to be aware of the privacy policy governing any site you visit. CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY Sid Harvey reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy. For this reason, you should regularly check our policy to ensure that it continues to meet your needs.Any questions or concerns can be forwarded to privacy@sidharvey.com. All emails will receive our prompt attention and response.
Top
Freight Policy
Freight Policy
TO: All Customer Service – Traffic Managers & Sales Representatives of all Vendors and Suppliers of Sid Harvey Industries, Inc. facilities and store locations
DATE: April 11, 2012
SUBJECT: VENDOR ROUTING INSTRUCTIONS – EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY
This letter is to inform you that Sid Harvey Industries, Inc. is now partnering with PLS Logistics as our primary transportation provider. The instructions below are for all suppliers and vendors when shipping to any Sid Harvey store, Sid Harvey customer as requested by authorized Sid Harvey personnel, Central Distribution Center, Andrews factory or our headquarters in Garden City, New York.
As a result, the following routing instructions are to be followed by all vendors for inbound collect ground freight destined to all locations and authorized customer’s shipments of Sid Harvey Industries, Inc.
Small Package Shipments
All small package ground shipments from 1 – 200 lbs shall be routed UPS Ground Collect to our account number 45W3A6. Sid Harvey Industries will no longer pay for freight and/or handling charges on vendor invoices. We also request our purchase order number to appear on the UPS Label. Oversized shipment, items that must remain upright or large quantities of small boxes (>18) within this weight break should move through PLS Logistics as an LTL shipment.
UPS Parcel shipments being paid for by Sid Harvey going to any Sid Harvey location or customer should not be process with a declared option selected; we carry separate insurance for this coverage. No parcel should contain items valued greater than $2,000 per parcel, Sid Harvey cost. Vendor is responsible to insure shipments are sufficiently package in the view of UPS to uphold any damage claim.
LTL Shipments and Truck Load (TL) Loads
All palletized LTL shipments above 200 lbs, under 750 cubic feet or 12 linear feet or considered oversized MUST be routed through PLS Logistics via one of our approved LTL carriers by calling the number listed below or emailing to:
PLS Logistics at 888-757-8261
Plsfreight1@plslogistics.com
We anticipate and appreciate your cooperation in this matter. FAILURE TO FOLLOW THE ABOVE INSTRUCTIONS MAY RESULT IN CHARGE-BACK OF FREIGHT COST.
I thank you for your cooperation and I am available to discuss further any individual concerns or suggestions that you may have in pursuing out goals, as well as supporting our vendors that support Sid Harvey’s.
Sincerely,
Jack DeCotiis
Sr. Vice President – Operations
Sid Harvey Industries, Inc.
